(悟)《雛月が 遅刻？》
Hinazuki is late?
《雛月は
｢ﾌﾟﾚｾﾞﾝﾄ あした 渡す｣と言った》
She said she was going to
give me my present today.
《徹夜で 何か作っていて
遅刻なら じゅうぶん あり得る》
If she was up all night
making something,
it makes sense that she'd be late...
≪(八代)悟｡
Satoru...
《けど…》
...but...
(八代)悟！
(悟)あっ は… はい！
Satoru!
Y-Yes!
(八代)どうした？ 悟｡
心配事でもあるのか？
What's wrong, Satoru?
Are you worried about something?
(児童たち)フフフ…｡
HOPE
Ice Hockey Club
1988 National Champions
(チャイム)
雛月！
Hinazuki!
誰か いないの!?
雛月！
Is anyone home?!
Hinazuki!
《まさか…》
Don't tell me...
《ゴム長靴？
大人の男のサイズだ》
Rubber boots?
An adult male's size...
《雪が降ったのは
おとといの夜》
It snowed the night before last.
《つまり それ以降に
大人の男が ここに来た》
In other words, an adult male
came here after that.
(男性)おい｡ どうすんだ？ これ｡
Hey.
What are we gonna do?
(子供たち)
♬｢ごにんばやしの ふえたいこ｣➡
Five court musicians
playing drums and fifes!
♬｢きょうは たのしい
ひなまつり｣
It's a fun Girls' Festival!
THURSDAY, MARCH 3rd, 1988
KAYO HINAZUKI DISAPPEARED
ERASED
＜あれから
俺は ２日間 学校を休んだ＞
After that, I stayed home
from school for two days.
《おふくろは 買い物かな？》
Is Mom out shopping?
(澤田)実は 最近 隣の市でも
似たような事件があったんだわ｡
Actually, a similar incident
happened in a neighboring city.
(澤田)
犯人は すぐ捕まったんだけども
They caught the culprit
soon afterwards, but now this?
すぐ これだべ？
こっちのは
まだ 犯人 分かんねえし➡
We don't know who did it yet,
再発防止に
全力 出さんといかんべさ｡
but we'd better do everything in our power
to prevent it from happening again.
(佐知子)
もちろん それもあるけどさ➡
Of course that's part of it,
but about clamping down on the press...
報道規制の件 学校とも話して
すぐに 連絡するから｡
I'll call you right after
I talk to the school.
(澤田)ああ｡
上には 俺からも話しとくわ｡
Okay. I'll talk to city hall, too.
(佐知子)ホント 頼むね｡
I'm counting on you.
《おふくろの元同僚｡
テレビ石狩の記者だな》
Mom's former co-worker...
A reporter for TV Ishikari.
こんな事件の記憶を
子供に残したくないからさ｡
The kids shouldn't have to
remember something like this.
(澤田)そうだべな｡
Agreed.
《こんな段階から 動いてたのか》
So this is where it started...
HOKU-HOKU BENTO
心配するのは分かるけど
悟のせいじゃないしょや｡
I know you're worried,
but it's not your fault, Satoru.
僕は 何の役にも立たなかった｡
そうかな？
I didn't make a difference.
I don't know about that.
僕は 雛月の独りぼっちを
なくしたかったんだ｡
I didn't want Hinazuki to be all alone.
それは できてたべさ｡
Then you succeeded.
足りなかった…｡
もっと 何か できた…｡
It wasn't enough.
There must have been something else.
後から 自分のせいなんて思うのは
思い上がりってもんだべ｡
Thinking it's your fault
after the fact is just pointless.
えっ？
一人一人の人間にできることなんて限られてるっしょ
There's only so much one person can do.
あんたも 私も｡
That holds true for me and you.
あしたからは 学校に行きな｡
一人でいたら 気が ふさぐべ｡
Go to school tomorrow.
Being alone here
only makes you depressed.
うん…｡
Okay.
さあ 冷める前に 食べるべ｡
Now let's eat before it gets cold.
うん｡
Yeah.
(八代)みんなには
黙っていたことがあるんだ｡➡
I've been keeping something from you.
実は 加代が 風邪で休んでいるというのは
嘘なんだ｡
Actually, I lied when I said
Kayo was at home with a cold.
家庭の事情により 祖母の家に
引き取られることになった｡
She moved to her grandmother's
home for personal reasons.
急なことで みんなに お別れを言えなかったが
加代は 札幌で 元気だそうだ｡
It happened so suddenly that she wasn't
able to say goodbye to you,
but I hear Kayo is doing well in Sapporo.
(児童)家出？
(児童)お母さんが➡
Ran away from home?
I heard her mother beat her!
暴力 ふるってたんだって｡
(児童)えーっ ひどい！
That's terrible!
(児童)でも よかったべさ｡
(児童)うん｡
Then it's better this way.
(カズ)悟｡
Satoru!
(カズ)気にすんな！
(オサム)そうだよ｡ また会えるよ｡
Don't worry!
Yeah! You'll see her again!
Satoru...
(八代)悟｡ 加代の話は
学校とＰＴＡが話し合って決めた｡
The school and the PTA had a discussion
and decided what to say about Kayo.
当分の間
この話に乗っかってくれ｡
For the time being,
go along with this story.
はい｡
Okay.
すまないな｡
I'm sorry.
報道は 規制されているようだが雛月の家の近くには
連日 警察関係の車両が止まっていた
It seems the press has been muzzled,
but a police vehicle has been parked
near Hinazuki's house
for the past several days.
＜この段階では 雛月の母親も
容疑者の一人であるらしい＞
Apparently her mother
is a suspect at this stage.
＜雛月失踪から わずか６日後…＞
Only six days after Hinazuki disappeared.
LOOKING FOR
AYA NAKANISHI
11 YEARS OLD
March 8th 1988
March 9th 1988
市の方から 指導があってな➡
The city has issued an advisory.
学区外へ出掛けるときは
必ず 保護者と 一緒に…｡
When you leave school grounds,
always be with a guardian.
A second child has disappeared.
＜２人目が失踪した｡
予想外の早さだった＞
It's sooner than I expected.
March 9th 1988
March 10th 1988
(ケンヤ)悟｡ 知ってるか？
隣の泉水小の中西 彩って子の話｡
Satoru... have you heard?
About Aya Nakanishi
from Izumi Elementary?
うん｡
Yeah.
(ケンヤ)家出して
おじいちゃんちに行ってるって➡
A friend of mine from Izumi Elementary
said she ran away
泉水小の友達から聞いた｡
and then went to live
with her grandfather.
雛月と そっくりだね｡
That sounds just like Hinazuki.
家出って話
嘘だろ｡
I'm sure the part
about running away is a lie.
これってさ
連続誘拐事件じゃないか？
My guess is
this is really a case of serial abductions.
March 10th 1988
March 11th 1988
細かいシチュエーションにこそ 差は あるものの
確実に 18年前と同じ時の流れに 乗り始めていた
There are differences in details,
but we've definitely begun to go down
the same flow of time as 18 years ago.
March 11th 1988
March 12th 1988
KAYO HINAZUKI
NEXT UP:
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL STUDENT MISSING
HOKKAIDO - CHILDREN'S WHEREABOUTS UNKNOWN
捜査は 公開に切り替わったがテレビ石狩は
事件の報道を 早朝と深夜帯に限定し
The investigation became public,
but TV Ishikari only ran news of the story
early in the morning and late at night,
市内の子供を持つ家庭では
テレビ石狩のみを視聴するよう 指導がなされた＞
and adults with children were advised
to only let them watch TV Ishikari.
≪(ドアの開く音)
≪(佐知子)ただいま～｡
I'm back!
March 12th 1988
March 13th 1988
＜雛月の家の近くに 朝も夜もいた警察車両も➡
中西 彩の事件後は たまにしか見なくなった＞
The police car that had been camping out
in front of Hinazuki's house day and night
only appeared sporadically
after the Aya Nakanishi disappearance.
＜捜査が 連続誘拐事件に
シフトしたのだろう＞
The focus of the investigation
must have shifted to "serial abductions."
＜娘の失踪から わずか10日後➡
Just ten days after her
daughter disappeared...
その母親が捨てた
ごみ袋の中には➡
Inside the garbage bag she threw out
編みかけの手袋が入っていた＞
were a pair of knit mittens.
(雛月)
《ﾌﾟﾚｾﾞﾝﾄ あした 渡すね｡ 約束》
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
うわああああー！
《ここは？》
Where am I?
《戻ったのか？ 2006年に》
Am I back?
In 2006...
(警察官)４丁目23番１号｡
被害者は 藤沼 佐知子 52歳｡➡
23-1, 4th Street...
The victim is Sachiko Fujinuma,
52 years old.
藤沼 悟 29歳を
重要参考人として 捜索中｡➡
We're searching for Satoru Fujinuma,
29 years old, as a suspect.
目撃情報あり｡ どうぞ｡
(警察官)了解｡
We do have eyewitness
information. Over.
Roger.
(悲鳴)
(警察官)《藤沼 悟…》
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
Wrong. You're wrong.
《違う… 違う…｡ 俺じゃ…》
It wasn't me...
《チクショー》
Dammit!
《雛月を助けられず
おふくろを殺され➡
I couldn't help Hinazuki...
Mom is still murdered...
俺が その容疑者》
and I'm the suspect!
《これが 今 目の前にある現実》
That's the reality I'm faced with.
《覚悟を決めろ》
Get ready!
《逃げるんだ》
Run away!
Episode 5
Getaway
《結局 橋の下か…》
In the end, I'm under a bridge.
《俺の想像力って…｡
まだ 報道されてるわけねえのに》
Some imagination I've got...
Even though I haven't
made the news yet...
《まずは 考えろ》
First off, I have to think.
《なぜ おふくろは殺された？
犯人の正体に気付いたから？》
Why was Mom murdered?
Because she realized
the identity of the culprit?
《アパートに
おふくろの携帯は あったか？》
Was her cell phone in the apartment?
《バッグは？
どっちもなかった》
What about her bag?
No, neither were there.
《つまり 犯人が持っていった？》
So the killer took them away?
《自分に関する情報を おふくろが
外に流していた 可能性があるからか？》
Because it was possible
Mom would've leaked info about him?
《くそっ！》
Dammit!
《頭が重い…》
My head feels heavy.
《せめて 今日一日
ゆっくり 眠りたい》
I want to sleep the day away.
[TEL](バイブレーターの音)
うん？
(高橋)まあ 食えよ｡
どうも｡
Here, eat.
Thanks.
(悟)今日は すみませんでした｡
I apologize for today.
(高橋)
初めてだな 無断欠勤するなんて｡
This is the first time you were absent
from work without permission.
片桐君も 心配してたぞ｡
Katagiri was worried about you, too.
君のことだから
事情があったんだろうが…｡
Knowing you, I'm sure
there's a reasonable explanation, but...
さあ まずは 食おうか｡
いただきます｡
Anyway, let's eat up first!
Thank you.
そうか｡ 母親と ケンカしたか｡
はい｡
I see.
So you had a fight
with your mother, huh?
Yes.
昔の人ってのは
堅いとこ あるからな｡
Old people can be set in their ways.
気が済むまで いていいけど
ちゃんと 母親とは仲直りしろよ｡
You can stay here as long as you want,
but you've gotta patch
things up with your mom.
はい｡
I will.
悟君も ビール飲むか？
いえ｡
You want a beer too, Satoru?
No.
あ～ 切らしてるわ｡
ちょっと 買ってくる｡
I'm out.
I'll go buy some more.
♬(鼻歌)
《やっぱ ちょっと うざい
兄貴肌の印象どおりだ》
My impression was right.
He is the "annoying big brother" type.
《嘘をついて すまない》
I'm sorry for lying to you.
The police received a tip
and hurried over.
通報を受けた警察が 駆け付けたところアパートの
住人の母親と思われる女性が死亡しているのを発見しました｡
They discovered the body of a woman
believed to be the mother
of the apartment's resident.
警察は現在行方が分からなくなっている 住人の男性が
事件に関与しているものとみて 行方を追っています｡
The police are currently
searching for the male resident
as a person of interest in the case.
《まんま 最悪の展開に
なってるじゃねえかよ》
This has taken a disastrous turn!
あっ…｡
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ](ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ)続いて ｽﾎﾟｰﾂです｡➡
And now, sports.
サｯカー日本代表は 今日 決戦の地
ドイツへと旅立ちました｡
Today the Japanese soccer team
left for Germany,
where the playoffs will be held.
《いいかげん 甘過ぎだぞ 俺》
I've been way too naïve!
《いや 店長を恨むな》
No. I can't blame the manager!
《あの人は いつも 正義の人だ｡
当然の行動なんだ》
He's always trying to do the right thing!
Of course he'd give me up!
《くそ野郎！》
Son of a bitch!
うわっ！
あっ！ ああ…｡
うん？
バカなの？
Are you stupid?
愛梨？
Airi...
(愛梨)あっ
愛梨って呼んでくれたね 悟さん！
You called me "Airi," Satoru.
携帯の電源
入れっ放しは駄目でしょ｡
You can't leave your phone on.
ＧＰＳで追跡されちゃうよ｡
They'll track you with GPS.
あっ…｡
何してるの？ 早く乗りなよ｡
えっ？
What are you doing?
Hop on!
逃げるんでしょ？
You want to get away, right?
すまない 片桐君｡
(愛梨)愛梨ね｡
I'm sorry, Katagiri.
It's "Airi."
２人乗りは おあいこだから｡
Riding double on the bike
makes us equals.
俺を家に入れても 平気なのか？
事件のことは 知ってんだろ？
You don't mind letting me in your house?
You do know what happened, right?
今日 店に 警察が来て
店長に 何か話してたよ｡
The police came to the shop today
and talked to the manager.
ニュースでも やってたね｡
それじゃあ どうして…｡
It was on the news, too.
Then why...
そんなの決まってるじゃん｡
It's obvious!
悟さんが あの お母さんを
殺すなんて あり得ない｡
There's no way you killed
your mom, Satoru.
そうか…｡ ありがとう｡
I see.
Thank you.
お礼なんていいよ｡
You don't need to thank me.
一番 悔しいはずの悟さんが
追われてるなんてそれこそ あり得ない｡
I can't believe they're chasing you,
the one who's grieving the most.
悟さんって
よくよく 事件に縁があるんだね｡
Though you really are connected
to a lot of crimes...
えっ？
NIPPON
SHOWA'S MOST SHOCKING CRIMES
ほら こないだ 店に忘れてたよ｡
Here.
You forgot it at the shop the other day.
付箋 挟んであったとこ
読ませてもらっちゃった｡
I read the part you had bookmarked
with an envelope.
あれって
悟さんの地元で 同世代でしょ？
It happened in your hometown
when you were a kid, right?
雛月 加代ちゃんが
亡くなった事件｡
Kayo Hinazuki's death...
ひな祭りの日に死んじゃうなんて 読んでて
泣いちゃった｡
To die on the day of the Girls' Festival...
I cried when I read that.
えっ ひな祭り？
Girls' Festival?
うん｡ ３月３日って｡
Yeah. March 3rd.
ちょっと ゆっくり してて｡
You can relax here.
愛梨
バイク 店に返してこなくっちゃ｡
I have to take the bike back to the shop.
絶対 部屋から出ちゃ駄目だよ｡
Don't even think about leaving this room.
KAYO HINAZUKI
(10 YEARS OLD)
《本の内容が 変わってる…》
The book's information has changed...
KAYO HINAZUKI
(11 YEARS OLD)
《つまり 変えられるんだ》
Then... it can be changed.
《もう一度 あっちに行けたら
雛月を…》
If I can go back there one more time,
I can save Hinazuki!
うん？
《そうだ｡ 愛梨の部屋だった》
That's right. I'm in Airi's room.
(愛梨)｢悟さんへ｣➡
Dear Satoru,
｢今日は 普段どおりの生活を
した方がいいと思うのでバイトに行ってきます｣
I think it would be a good idea
if I went about my normal routine today,
so I'm going to work.
｢家族は
10時に外出するそうです｣➡
My family will probably
leave the house around ten.
｢帰りは
20時 過ぎると言ってました｣➡
They said they'll be back
after eight tonight.
｢家の鍵と バイクの鍵は
時計の横｣➡
The house key and bike key
are next to the clock.
｢愛梨の携帯番号は…｣
My cell phone number is...
SASAOKA
《片桐… じゃないのか》
It's not "Katagiri."
「高橋」　いや～ 本当に ありがとうございます西園先生｡
「西園」　いや いいんだ｡
Thank you so much, Mr. Nishizono!
That's all right.
君のお父さんには
いつも 世話になっているからね｡
I'm in your father's debt.
いえいえ そんなことないっすよ｡
父も 大喜びっす｡
No, no. Not at all.
My dad was overjoyed.
信号一つ 横断歩道一つでこんなに
人の流れが変わるなんてって｡
He said one stoplight
and one pedestrian crossing
totally changed the flow
of customers for us.
(西園)それは 君のお父さんが
優れた経営者だということさ｡
That has more to do with your
father's business acumen.
僕は 少しばかり
手助けをしたにすぎないよ｡➡
All I did was give him a little boost.
それに もともと
あそこは 通学路だしね｡➡
Besides, it's a school route.
市議会でも 時折
話題になる案件の一つだった｡
We would occasionally talk
about it at city council meetings.
店長 お疲れさまです！
あがりま～す！
Bye, Manager! I just finished.
おう！ お疲れ 愛梨君！
Good job, Airi!
あっ それは？
(愛梨)ああ 持ち帰りのピザです｡
What's that?
Take-out pizza.
何だ 言えよ｡
たまには 俺 おごるからさ｡
You should've told me!
I can treat you once in a while.
ありがとうございます｡
Thank you!
でも いいんです｡
友達が食べるやつですから｡
But that's okay.
This is for my friend.
そ… そう 友達ね｡
女の子かな？ アハハ…｡
O-Oh, your friend...
A girl, maybe?
(愛梨)お先に失礼しまーす｡
I'll see you tomorrow!
(西園)カワイイ子じゃないか｡
She's cute.
(高橋)あっ すみません｡でも まあそのまだ
17歳ですし 幼いっつうか…｡
Pardon me!
But, well, she's only 17,
and still immature...
(西園)フッ｡
(西園) じゃあ
僕も そろそろ帰るとするか｡
Well, I should be on my way as well.
(高橋)お疲れさまです｡
Thank you again!
CHINESE CAFETERIA
(高橋)愛梨君！
(愛梨)うん？
Airi!
店長｡
(高橋)はい 忘れ物｡
Manager!
Here, you forgot this.
今 サービス期間中だろ？
(愛梨)あっ すみません｡
Part of the sales promotion, remember?
Thank you.
それで 悟君のことなんだけど…｡
(愛梨)えっ？
Also... about Satoru...
俺は 悟君が母親を…➡
I can't believe that he murdered his...
いや あんな事件を起こすなんて
考えられねえんだよ｡
I mean, that he did any of that.
(愛梨)同感です｡
I agree!
もし 彼に会うようなことがあったら力になってやってくれよな｡
(愛梨)はい！
If you happen to run into him,
do what you can to help him out.
I will!
俺も応援するから
そんときは 連絡くれよ｡
We're all on the same side,
so contact me too if you see him.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
《こんなこと調べて
犯人に近づけるのか？》
Can I close in on the killer
by investigating like this?
《うん？
｢市内で ３年前に児童誘拐事件｣》
A child abduction
in the city three years ago...
《そういや そんな事件あったな》
Come to think of it, I recall that.
《｢事件から３週間後
容疑者 逮捕｣》
The suspect was arrested
three weeks later.
《｢しかし 容疑者は
一貫して 無罪を主張｣》
But he claimed he was innocent
the whole time.
《何だろう？ この感じ…》
What is this feeling?
《何か 引っ掛かる…》
Something bothers me about this.
「高橋」　あっ｡
「愛莉」　 警察に 何の用ですか？ 店長｡
「高橋」　愛梨君…｡
What do you want with the police...
Manager?
Airi!
悟さんを助けてやれって…｡
店長も応援したいって 言ったじゃん｡
You told me to help Satoru.
You said we were all on the same side!
That's what you said!
ち… 違うんだ 愛梨君！
俺は その… 君のことが心配で｡
Y-You have the wrong idea, Airi!
I, um, was worried about you...
(高橋)うっ！➡
ああっ！
じゃあ どうして
最初から そう言ってくれないの！
Then why didn't you
tell me that from the start?!
愛梨だって
店長のこと 信じたかったのに！
I wanted to trust you, Manager!
「高橋」　き… 君のことが心配で…｡
「愛莉」　そこは 信じるよ｡
I-I was worried about you.
I believe that.
(高橋)ご… ごめん｡
(愛梨)店長 お願い…｡
I'm sorry.
Manager... please...
愛梨のことが心配ならお世話になってるこの家に
警察を呼ぶような まねは やめてください｡
If you're worried about me,
don't call the police over to my house.
(愛梨)ごめんね 悟さん｡
I'm sorry, Satoru.
何も謝ることない｡
むしろ ありがとう｡
You have nothing to apologize for.
In fact, thank you.
君のおかげで
ずいぶん 体も休まったよ｡
You gave me a chance to rest.
(愛梨)あの家は もう戻れないよ｡
いや それで よかったんだ｡
You can't go back to that house now.
Yeah, but it's better this way.
そういや あの家は
君の実家じゃないんだね｡
By the way, it's not really
your parents' house, is it?
うん｡ 母の兄夫婦の家なんだ｡
愛梨の実家って 田舎でさ➡
No.
My mom's big brother
and his wife live there.
My parents live out in the country.
高校 通うなら 下宿することになりそうだから
いっそのこと 千葉に来いって言ってくれて｡
I was going to find a boarding house
so I could commute to high school,
but they invited me
to stay with them in Chiba.
もう一つ 聞いていいか？
何？
Can I ask you one more question?
What is it?
愛梨｡ 君は どうして
俺のことを信じられるんだ？
Airi, how can you believe in me?
信じられるからじゃないんだ｡
信じたいの｡
It isn't that I "can."
I want to believe in you.
(愛梨)愛梨が まだ 小学生のころ
父さんと二人で買い物に行ったの｡
When I was still in elementary school,
my dad and I went grocery shopping.
(愛梨)父さんのジャケットの ポケットから
チョコレートが出てきた｡
A chocolate bar fell out of his pocket.
小さな町だし 店主も知り合いで盗んだことは認めて
謝罪すれば それでいいって言ってくれた｡
It was a small town
and we knew the owner.
If he admitted to stealing it
and apologized,
the owner said he would
let the matter drop.
でも 父さんは
絶対に認めなかった｡
But Dad refused to admit it.
優しかった父さんが
大声で叫ぶのを 初めて聞いた｡➡
Dad was a kind man.
That was the first time I heard him yell.
店主も
警察を呼ぶしかなくなって…｡➡
The owner felt obliged to call the police,
地元の農業組合の役員だった 父さんは懲戒処分で 停職３カ月｡
and Dad, a member
of the local agricultural coop,
was suspended for three
months as punishment.
「愛莉」　《愛梨 ずっと見てたから 知ってるよ！》
《お父さんは やってないよ！》
I know! I saw the whole thing!
You didn't do anything, Dad!
(愛梨)父さんは 組合を辞めて
離婚して 家を出ていったの｡➡
Dad quit the coop,
got a divorce, and left home.
母さんは本当は 盗んだんじゃないかって 思ってたみたい｡
I guess Mom thought
he really did steal it.
(愛梨)愛梨の信じたいは
自分のためだよ｡
I want to believe you for my own sake.
誰かに 信じてほしいの
裏返しなんだよ｡
It's the flip side to someone
saying "please believe me."
君は 家に戻れ｡
Go back home.
警察には 俺に脅されて
かくまったことにしろ｡
Tell the police I threatened you,
forcing you to hide me.
バカなの？
一人で逃げ切れるわけないし➡
Are you stupid?
There's no way you can get away
by yourself, and I refuse to tell them that.
そんなこと言わないし｡
その ｢バカなの？｣ってのは
やめてくれねえかな？
Would you stop asking me if I'm stupid?
フッ｡
とにかく➡
Anyway, I'll at least bring you
a change of clothes, Satoru.
悟さんの着替えとかだけでも
持ってくるよ｡
(愛梨)《店長
あの後 通報しなかったんだ》
Manager...
After that, he didn't make
a report to the police.
[TEL](メールの着信音)
(愛梨)えっ？
Incoming Mail
Sachiko Fujinuma's Phone
えっ？ 何 これ？
What is this?
This is Satoru Fujinuma.
Stay right where you are.
What does it mean?
どういうこと？
悟さん
お母さんの携帯 見つけたの？
Satoru found his mom's phone?
どうやって…｡
How?
《違う｡ 犯人からだ｡
｢その場を動くな｣？》
No!
It's from the killer!
"Stay right where you are"?
えっ？
《う… 嘘でしょ!?》
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
嘘…｡
No way...
No way!
うっ！
(せき)